等一下  在进屋之前我要你知道
Wait. Before we go in, I just want you to know that
我爱你
I love you.
我蜜月时玩得很高兴
I had a great time on our honeymoon.
我等不及要跟你共度一生了
I can't wait to spend the rest of our life together.
你还戴着那条贝壳项链
You're sticking with the shell necklace, huh?
你们回来了
You're back!
快进来
Come on in!
你们蜜月玩得开心吗
How was the honeymoon?
我们很开心  最棒的是
So much fun. But the best part is,
我们认识了一对很棒的夫妇
we met this great couple on the flight back.
那是最棒的吗
That was the best part?
蜜月过得不错啊  小子
Good honeymooning, tiger.
他们很酷  他们也是去度蜜月的
They're really cool. They were on their honeymoon too.
他们人超好  就住在城里
They're terrific.They live here in the city.
我们能打电话给他们吗  现在打会不会太快了
Can we go call them? Is it too soon to call?
我想打给他们
I wanna call.
抱歉  我们很兴奋
I'm sorry. We're just kind of excited.
我们终于认识一对夫妇朋友了
We finally have a couple to hang out with.
夫妇朋友  你是指两个人吗
A couple? Like two people?
像是一  二  两个人吗
Like one, two people?
那不一样  葛瑞格跟珍妮结婚了
This is different. Greg and Jenny are in a relationship.
葛瑞格跟珍妮
Greg and Jenny?
"葛瑞格  我是钱德勒  这是莫妮卡"
"Hi, Greg. I'm Chandler. This is Monica"
"嗨  莫妮卡  她是珍妮"
"Hi, Monica. This is Jenny."
"嗨  珍妮  嗨  葛瑞格"
"Hi, Jenny. Hi, Greg."
-他们真的很棒  如果你们  -你知道吗
- They're great. If you just got a chance... - You know what?
快送我们纪念品  然后滚出去
Why don't you just give us our souvenirs and get out of here.
-我们没来得及...  -你开玩笑吧
- We didn't get a chance to... - You've gotta to be kidding me!
我们没给任何人买礼物
We didn't get anything for anyone.
好漂亮的项链
Yeah. Nice necklace.
这个可以送给你
That you can have.
你们好呀
Hello.
-欢迎你们回来  -蜜月玩得可好
- Welcome home. - How was the honeymoon?
太棒了  你们呢  你们要有宝宝了
Great! How about you? You're having a baby!
-你看  我有宝宝的B超  -太棒了
- Look, I have a sonogram picture. - Good.
罗斯  宝宝遗传了你的黑色卷发
Ross, it's got your wavy, black lines.
现在罗斯知道了  到底是怎么发生的
Now that Ross knows, can you tell us how'd it happen?
在什么时候  你们做了几次
When did it happen? How many times does it happen?
莫妮卡  那么问是不对的
Monica, that's not right.
从你们在哪里做开始说吧
Start with where.
事情发生在六个星期前
It happened about six weeks ago.
我回到家  发现罗斯也在
I just got home from work and Ross was already there.
他跟乔伊在一起玩
Guess he'd been hanging out with Joey.
别客气  兄弟
You're welcome, buddy.
对  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
我有很多事要做  罗斯很好心
I had a lot of work to do, and Ross, nice guy that he is,
主动说要帮忙
offered to help me out.
我们边喝酒边聊天
And then we had a little wine, we got to talking.
接下来罗斯突然就对我采取了主动
And next thing you know, out of nowhere, Ross comes on to me.
这很容易让人误会
That's a little misleading.
-什么  -你刚刚说的谎话
- What is? - The lie you just told.
-我说是你主动的  -没错
- That you came on to me? - There's the one!
但那是真的  老实一点吧
But you did. Let's be honest.
没错  老实一点吧
Yes, let's.
那不重要
It's not important.
重要的是我们要生孩子了
What's important is, we're having a baby,
谁先泡"随"并不重要
and it doesn't matter who came on to who.
是"谁"才对
"Whom."
没错
That's right.
你先吻我的
You know you kissed me first.
什么  是你求我吻你的
What? You were begging to kiss you!
你处处给我发送暗号
You were sending me signals all over the place!
-我向你发暗号  -对
- I was sending signals? - Yeah.
谁觉得是我向罗斯
Please. Okay. Anyone in this room think
发送乞求暗号的
that I'd actually send Ross begging signals?
请举手
Please, show of hands.
别人怎么想并不重要
You know, it doesn't matter what people believe!
重要的是发生了什么
What matters is what happened.
罗斯  跟我解释一下暗号的事
Okay, so these signals, Ross, explain this to me,
或许我得小心一点
'cause maybe I need to be more careful.
我正在发送讯号吗
Am I sending these signals right now?
你知道吗  瑞秋  别纠结这个问题了
You know what? You know what? Rachel, just drop it.
拜托告诉我  我是怎么求你的
No, please. Show me how I begged you.
我可以证明  我都录在录影带里了
I can show you! I have it on videotape.
那不过是一种表达方法
It's an expression.
我不敢相信他录下他们做爱的经过
I can't believe he taped the two of them having sex.
对  你录之前要先告诉对方才行
Yeah. You gotta tell a girl before you tape her.
那是菜鸟才会犯的错误
Such a rookie mistake.
你知道谁家有很棒的摄影机吗
You know who has a great camera?
葛瑞格跟珍妮
Greg and Jenny?
你还想打电话给他们吗
Do you still want to call them?
-我想打给他们  -快打吧
- I want to call them. - Let's call them.
问他们有没有买纪念品送给朋友
Ask them if they brought their friends souvenirs.
喂  第八街外送餐厅
Hello. 8th Street Deli?
快挂掉  光跟他们说话你就会食物中毒
Hang up. You get food poisoning just talking to that place.
-抱歉  打错了  -来吧  宝贝
- Sorry, wrong number. - Here you go, babe.
喂  又是外送餐厅
Hello? It's the deli again!
好吧  我要吃三明治
All right, I'll have a sandwich.
我觉得这个电话号码是错的
I don't think this number's right.
-怎么  -你们拿到假电话了
- What? - You got fake-numbered.
-什么  没有人会那么做  -我们会
- What? People don't do that. - Oh, I think we do.
他们给了我们假号码
They gave us a fake number?
-他们为什么要那么做  -我不知道
- Why would they do that? - I don't know.
跟你聊天很开心
You were a delight to talk to.
你问了一些很有见解的问题
You asked all those insightful, great questions.
你也很风趣  一直在开玩笑
And you've never been funnier. I mean, joke, joke, joke!
你真的很耍宝
You were a hoot!
别担心了  你们还有我跟菲比
Don't worry about it. You still got me and Phoebe.
对不起  我不要葛瑞格跟珍妮的退货
Excuse me, I don't want Greg and Jenny's rejects.
瑞秋不肯跟我说话  她连门都不肯开
Rachel won't talk to me. She won't open the door.
我很好奇是为什么  变态
I wonder why, pervert.
好吧  我不是变态
Okay, listen, I am not a pervert.
变态都是那么说的
That's, like, the pervert motto.
举起你的右手  把左手插进裤子里
Raise your right hand, put your left hand down your pants
再重复那句话
and repeat that.
我不是故意要拍瑞秋
Filming Rachel was not something I planned.
事情的经过是这样的  乔伊可以帮我作证
Okay, look. Here's what happened. Joey can back me up on this.
还记得一个半月前  我跑去问你一个问题吗
A month and a half ago, remember I came to you with a problem?
我的私人问题
The personal thing?
-什么私人间题  -关于性的问题
- What personal thing? - About sex?
我好几个月没有性生活了
That I hadn't had sex in months?
我刚才就知道你的是哪件事
Yeah, I knew what you were talking about.
你有空吗
Do you have a minute?
我想谈一件我很难启齿的事
I'd like to talk about something I'm uncomfortable talking about.
没问题
Sure.
你跟你妈一起洗澡如何
How about you showering with your mom?
我已经想好问题了
I actually had a topic in mind.
我进入了干涸期
I'm kind of going through a dry spell,
在性生活方面
sex-wise.
-有好几个月了吗  -五个月...
- For, like, months? - Five, to be...
骗人的  是六个月
...lying. Six.
六个月  那一定很难熬
Six months? That's rough.
没有那么糟糕
It's not all bad.
我学着去欣赏生活中的一些小事  譬如说
I'm learning to appreciate the small things in life, like...
鸟的叫声跟天空的颜色
...the sound of a bird and the color of the sky.
天空是蓝色的  罗斯  我昨天才做过爱
The sky's blue, Ross. And I had sex yesterday.
拜托  帮帮我  我今晚有约会
Please help me. I have a date tonight.
我得顺利达阵  我很担心自己的健康
It has to go well. I'm scared for my health.
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
我有个点子  我想出一个故事
I got something. It's this story that I came up with.
非常浪漫  听到这个故事的女人都会心动
Very romantic. I swear any woman that hears it is putty.
-真的吗  说吧  -好
- Really? Tell it to me. - Okay.
你听完后定会想跟我上床
Now, you're gonna want to have sex with me when you hear it.
记住  那只是一个故事
Remember, it is just the story.
我会试着控制自己
I'll try to control myself.
好
Okay.
多年前  我在西欧自助旅行
Years ago, I was backpacking across Western Europe...
你在西欧自助旅行
You were backpacking across Western Europe?
你再干涸六个月去吧  罗斯
Have a nice six more months, Ross.
好吧  抱歉  求求你
Okay, okay. I'm sorry. Please, please.
你去了西欧  然后
You were in Western Europe, and...?
我在巴塞罗那郊外
I was just outside Barcelona,
在第比达包山脚下健行
hiking in the foothills of Mount Tibidabo.
我走到小路的尽头
I was at the end of this path,
来到一片林中空地  发现了一座湖
and I came to a clearing and there was a lake.
它非常隐密  四周都是高大的树木
Very secluded. There were tall trees all around.
那里非常安静  美极了
It was dead silent. Gorgeous.
我看到在湖的对面
And across the lake I saw
有个美女在洗澡
a beautiful  woman bathing herself.
但她在哭
But she was crying.
为什么
Why?
酒真的很棒
This is great wine.
是法国酒
It's from France.
法国在欧洲
In Europe.
就在西欧
Western Europe.
几年前
You know, a few years ago
我在西欧自助旅行
I was backpacking across Western Europe.
-真的吗  -等一下  后面的故事更精彩
- Really? - Wait, it gets better.
对  我在巴塞罗那
Yeah, I was in Barcelona.
我在巴塞罗那念过一年书
I studied for a year in Barcelona.
总之我在健行...
So anyway, I was hiking...
-我喜欢健行  -那真的太棒了
- I love hiking! - That's great!
我在第比达亚波山脚下健行...
I was hiking along the foothills of Mount Tibidaybo...
我想是"第比达包山"才对
I think it's "Tibidabo."
你想来讲这个故事吗
Okay, do you want to tell the story?
你怎么来了  约会还顺利吗
What are you doing here? How'd your date go?
太棒了 我正要过街去和她做爱
Great. I'm across the street having sex right now.
你的故事烂透了
Your story sucks.
如果不起作用  一定是你说的方法不对
Look, if it didn't work, it's because you didn't tell it right.
-告诉我你是怎么说的  -不  我不想谈
- Show me how you did it. - No, I don't want to.
你上次看到裸女是什么时候的事
How long since you seen a girl naked?
我在西欧自助旅行
I was backpacking across Western Europe...
我没有感觉
I'm not feeling it.
我在巴塞罗那郊外健行
I was outside Barcelona, hiking...
罗斯  我并没觉得欲火焚身  你呢
No, Ross, I'm not hot. Are you hot?
我六个月没做爱  每天都欲火焚身
It's been six months. I'm always hot.
你讲故事不够动人  你根本就不相信它
You're not selling the story. You don't believe it.
我得走了  我有约会  但试试这招
I gotta go, I got a date. But try this.
学我在试镜前做的那一招
Do what I do when I'm preparing for an audition.
不  我帮你设置好录像机
No. I'll set you up with my video camera
你可以自拍看看哪里做错了
and you could record yourself and see what you're doing wrong.
我会试试看
I'll try that.
已经设定好了  可以拍了
Alright, now, you're all set up. You're good to go.
-按下录影键就可以了  祝你好运 -谢谢
- Just hit record. - Good luck. Thanks.
乔伊  如果你跟女人约会出了问题
Hey, Jo, listen. If you ever have any problem with the ladies,
我可以帮你
you know I'll help you out.
那对我来说意义重大
That means a lot to me, man.
你好啊
Hello.
需要我帮你效劳吗  要擦镜头吗
Can I get you anything? Lens cleaner?
电池还有电吗
Your battery okay?
罗斯  谢天谢地你在这里  快帮帮我
Ross, thank God you're here. You have to help me.
你在自言自语吗
Were you talking to yourself?
那样说会比较不丢脸  对  没错
That's less embarrassing. Yes. Yes, I was.
她一走进来  我一分心
So when she came in, I got distracted
就完全忘记了录影机的事
and totally forgot about the camera.
录影机拍录下了整个经过
It kept rolling and recorded everything.
我们得看看那卷录影带
Yeah, we're gonna need to see that tape.
真是个好主意  那会让瑞秋原谅我
What a great idea! That'll get Rachel to forgive me.
那对她来说不公平  忘了录影带的事吧
You know what? It's not fair to her. Let's forget the tape.
谢谢
Thank you.
-不行  -你说得对
- No. - You're right.
-乔伊  不行  -我了解
- Joey, no. - Loud and clear.
我不明白为什么葛瑞格和珍妮
I still don't get why Greg and Jenny
要给我们假的电话号码
would give us a fake number.
如果他们是这方面的老手
You know, if they knew what they were doing,
甚至都不会给你们真名
they probably didn't give you real names, either.
或许有人会给假电话号码
Maybe people give out fake numbers,
但没有人会给假名
but they don't give out fake names.
是吗  嗨  肯·亚当斯很高兴能认识你
Oh, yeah? Hi. Ken Adams. Nice to meet you.
瑞吉娜·费兰吉
Regina Phalange.
-真不懂  我们没做错事  -就是嘛
- I just don't get it. We didn't do anything wrong. - I know.
虽然你说了很多冷笑话
Although you did tell an awful lot of jokes.
你说很好笑啊  快讲笑话吧
You said they were funny. Joke, joke, joke!
讲笑话...
Joke, joke...
可能是你问了太多问题害的
Or maybe it was your questions.
我的问题怎么了
What about my questions?
你问了太多问题
The sheer volume.
像是跟谜题王坐在一起
It was like flying with the Riddler.
-你又在讲笑话吗  -你又在问问题吗
- I'm soory. Was that another joke? - Was that another question?
罗斯还在吗
Is Ross still here?
他走了  但他告诉我们发生了什么事
No, Rach, he's gone, but, listen, he told us what happened.
听起来真的是个误会
It does sound like an honest mistake.
是吗  如果我把我跟你做爱的过程录下来
Really? How would you like it if I had sex with you
你会有什么感觉呢
and I taped it?
算了吧
Oh, forget it.
他来了  我孩子他爹
There he is, the father of my child,
西村的黄片之王
the porn king of the West Village.
那是个意外  行吗
Look, it was an accident, okay?
我觉得很内疚  我发誓我还没有看过它
I feel bad that happened, but I swear, I didn't even watch it.
总之  拿去吧
Anyway, here.
或许亲手毁了它  你会觉得舒服一点
I thought you might be more comfortable destroying it yourself.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么
What?
-你们不想看这玩意吧  -我们当然想
- You don't want to see this, do you? - Hell, yeah!
我不会让你们看这个
I am not gonna show you this.
我们不是要看性爱镜头
Not the sex part.
只是想看你们怎么开始的
Just the stuff leading up to it.
算了  让她毁掉吧
Forget it. She's destroying it.
我们会想其他办法
Okay, fine, fine. We'll think of another way
解决"谁先主动"的问题
to put the "who came on to who" thing to rest.
快想
Come on now, think!
别想这事了  菲比  那是瑞秋的录影带
Forget it, Phoebe, okay? It's Rachel's tape,
她想怎么处置它是她的自由
and she can do whatever she wants with it.
她想毁了它  别说了
And she wants to destroy it, so end of story.
-我想看  -什么
- I want to see it. - What?
你显然不希望大家看这盘录影带
Clearly, you don't want people to see this tape.
我也不想让大家看
I don't want people to see this tape, either.
但你非常不希望我们看
But you so badly don't want us to see it
让我想要看个究竞  明白吗
that it makes me want to see it. Do you see?
我们到底要不要看录影带
Are we watching the tape or not?
我不让别人看是为了保护你
I don't want people to see it for your sake.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我想你不希望他们看到你求我
I think you don't want them to see you begging me.
-瑞秋  求你了  -这算是预告部份
- Rachel, please? - Oh, a little preview.
好吧  我要这卷录影带证明
Fine. Fine. But I want the record to show
我是想保护你
that I tried to take the high road.
因为再过五分钟我会说...
Because in about five minutes, I'm gonna be saying...
好吧  要开始了
Okay, here we go.
你好啊  需要我帮你效劳吗
Hello. Can I get you anything?
我好开心
I'm so happy.
谢天谢地你在这里  罗斯  快帮帮我
Thank God you're here, Ross. Help me.
你在自言自语吗
Were you talking to yourself?
-我出现了  -你就要怀孕了
- There I am. - You're gonna get pregnant.
我搞砸了
I screwed up so bad.
好几个星期前我告诉莫妮卡
I told Monica that I'd send
我会把喜帖寄出去
all those wedding invitations weeks ago.
你没有寄
You didn't do it?
我把它们放在办公桌上  直到今天才想起来
I put them in my desk at work, and forgot about them until today.
亲爱的  没关系的
Sweetie, it's okay.
客人都来了  我没事的
Everybody made it to the wedding. I'm fine.
-但你把我的手弄痛了  -我知道
- Kind of hurting my hand though. - I know.
我竟然会做出这种事
I can't believe I did this,
何况莫妮卡每天都在嘱咐我这件事
especially after Monica went on and on and on about it.
喜帖在这里  瑞秋  小心点  瑞秋
"Okay, Rachel. Here are the invitations, Rachel. Be very careful, Rachel.
拜托  别在喜帖附近喝东西  瑞秋
Please, drinking no liquids around the invitations, Rachel."
你们在我们的喜帖上面做爱了吗
Did you do it on our invitations?
我们没在寄出去的喜帖上做
Not on the ones we sent out.
你们在我们裱起来的喜帖上面做爱了
So just the ones you gave back to us and we had framed?
一切都发生得太快了
Can you believe it's already happening?
感觉上他们像是昨天才订婚
It seems like yesterday they just got engaged.
我知道
I know.
还记得他们订婚那一晚吗
Remember that night they got engaged?
你跟我差一点...
How you and I almost...
我记得我们差一点就做了
Oh, I remember how we almost.
你觉得我们当时真的会做吗
You think we would've gone through with it?
如果没被逮到的话
If we haven't gotten caught.
你觉得我们会做吗
You think we would have done it?
我知道我想做  但我不知道你想不想
I know I wanted to. I just wasn't sure if you wanted to.
我也想
Oh, I wanted to.
那么我们两个都想
So we both wanted to.
有意思
Interesting.
总之
Anyway,
这样的结果或许是最好的
it probably worked out for the best.
没错
Yeah, sure.
再过十秒他就要吻我了
In about 10 seconds, he kisses me.
再过五秒你们就会知道为什么
In about 5 seconds, you'll see why.
我有没有跟你说过
Ross, did I ever tell you about the time
我到西欧自助旅行的事
that I went backpacked through Western Europe?
准备看她求我吧
Get ready to see some begging.
是你对罗斯主动的
Oh, you came on to Ross!
什么
What?
现在我好开心
Now I'm so happy.
-你这是什么意思  -你用了欧洲的故事
- What are you talking about? - You used the Europe story!
那是你想做爱时会用的魔法故事
That's the magic story you use when you want to have sex!
你怎么知道那个故事
How do you know about that story?
是一个家伙告诉我朋友艾琳的
My friend Irene heard it from some guy.
就是我
Some guy!
不  她说那个家伙叫做肯·亚当斯
No, she told me that his name was Ken Adams.
我就是肯·亚当斯
Ken Adams!
看来大家都知道欧洲的故事
So, people are familiar with the Europe story?
关于"谁主动"的问题
Yeah. Listen. About that, the "who came on to who" thing
真的不重要
really doesn't matter.
反正该发生的总会发生
I mean, it would have happened either way.
就算你不主动  我也会主动
If you had't initiated it, I know I would have.
那是个神奇的夜晚
It was an amazing night.
没错  确实很神奇
It was. It was an amazing night.
你觉得它看起来也很神奇吗
You think it looked amazing?
我不知道
I don't know.
我真的没看
I mean, I honestly didn't watch it.
是  我也没看
Yeah, me neither.
还没看
Yet.
看的话应该会很奇怪
That may be weird.
对  会很奇怪
Yeah, it would be really weird.
-祝你好运  -祝你好运
- Good luck. - Good luck to you.
-我可以消音吗  -麻烦你了
- Mind if I mute? - Oh, please.
我们开始脱衣服了
There go the clothes.
你脱衣服的速度真快
You are undressing awfully quickly.
我六个月没做了  瑞秋
Six months, Rachel. Six months.
-我们看起来很不错  -我也那么觉得
- We look pretty good. - I was gonna say.
-你皮肤晒得很漂亮  -谢谢
- Nice tan. - Thank you.
那个周末我才去过海边
I'd just gone to the beach that weekend.
你有在健身吗
Have you been working out?
我一直在健身
I have been working out.
这比我之前的经验要好得多...
This is so much better than I ever...
那可不太雅观
Oh, that's not pretty.
-快点关掉  -不
- Make it stop. Make it stop. - Oh, no!
喂  葛瑞格吗
Hello, Greg?
我是飞机上跟你们见过面的莫妮卡
Hi, this is Monica from the plane.
听着  你给我的电话号码  853...
Listen, the number that you gave me, 8-5-3...
那是他们的旧号码
That is their old number.
他们搬家之后  珍妮老是给别人他们的旧号码
Jenny's been giving it out since they moved!
那真像珍妮的作风
Jenny! That is so Jenny!
你们下星期六能跟我们一起去玩吗
Listen. How would you like to get together next Saturday?
好吧  星期天呢
Okay, how about Sunday?
下星期呢
Okay, the week after that?
下下星期呢
The week after that?
你知道吗
You know what, Greg?
我们幽默风趣
We are good, interesting,
善于提问
funny people with good questions.
如果你跟你的宝贝珍妮没发现...
And if you and your precious Jenny can't see that, then...
一月十五日
January 15?
到时候见
We'll see you then! Okay.